<review>
<unique_id>
0743518144:ok~_but_i_think_the_keirsey_temperment_test_is_more_accurate_-_and_cheaper.:jen_"the_truthsayer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
389
</unique_id>
<asin>
0743518144
</asin>
<product_name>
Now, Discover Your Strengths: Books: Marcus Buckingham,Donald O. Clifton
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Ok~ but I think the Keirsey Temperment Test is more accurate - and cheaper.
</title>
<date>
September 10, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jen "the truthsayer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
DE, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This book has its good points. If anything, it helps you put into words what you want  from a supervisor, but it is not very accurate. The online test does not account for a difference between when 2 of their options are both exactly like you, or if they don't describe you at all. This messes up the results, and it did not describe me very well. I am not just in denial. I have taken a lot of personality type tests, like the Keirsey Temperment sorter and have a pretty good idea of my strengths. So, although this book is pretty good in making you understand the importance of incouraging your strengths, it still leaves you wondering about how you fit in to their terminology.

As for using this book as a manager to better serve your employees, I'v seen it done and it does not necessarily work because the strengths spit out for people were not wholly accurate. The company I work for has done this, and most of the people who were shifted around to better serve their strengths (according to this book) are very unhappy in their new positions.

Your money can be spent better elsewhere. I say its only worth about $10
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0895261715:repellent_sale_of_conservativism:e._david_swan
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
622
</unique_id>
<asin>
0895261715
</asin>
<product_name>
The Conservative Mind: From Burke to Eliot: Books: Russell Kirk
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
32 of 95
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Repellent Sale of Conservativism
</title>
<date>
August 18, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
E. David Swan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
South Euclid, Ohio USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The fatalistic view of Conservativism is expressed by Kirk even before the first chapter concludes as he states, "[Edmund] Burke, could he see our century, never would concede that a consumption-society, so near suicide, is the end for which Providence has prepared man".  But wait. The Conservative Mind was first published in 1953, the mythical golden age of America with Ward and June Cleaver and Normal Rockwell. Meanwhile, Burke, a contemporary of the 18th century is pining for the 14th century. What a depressing ideology to think that we always live in the worst of times.

There are certain ideological threads that carry throughout the book including a belief in the stratification of society. Voting should be the privilege of a small minority rather than universal democracy which Kirk saw as contributing to a degradation of society. Kirk writes, "What men really are seeking, or ought to seek, is not the right to govern themselves, but the right to be governed well" but what he offers is a lack of true representation. The author pines for the days of the aristocrat and although he defines the elites by wealth, intellect and lineage he clearly includes race and gender. Is it so surprising that Kirk lauds some of the worst racists in American history like Nathanial Bedford Forrest whom he describes as `magnificent' before quoting his racist vitriol? In a particularly galling move he referrers to pro-slavery advocate John C. Calhoun as a `defender of minorities' and praises John Randolph for, among other things, opposing doctrines of racial equality. Kirk goes on about Calhoun's support for states rights but his support only extended to southern states as he supported the Fugitive Slave Act which forced federal officials and law officials in Northern states to return runaway slave under penalty of $1000 fine. He supported laws that would make it illegal for northerners to even protest slavery. For Calhoun states rights were nothing more than a self serving attempt to keep slavery safe. Kirk shows his own racist stripes when he refers to northern `anti-slavery agitation' and supports Calhoun for choosing racial preservation over liberty, although Calhoun has an extremely warped view of liberty. One wonders if Kirk could even fathom the supreme irony in stating the Calhoun mounted a `strong protest against domination by class or region'.

Another thread is his desire to see the reunification of church and state. The duty of the church is to keep the unclean masses in line. Quoting Samuel Coleridge, the author makes it clear that the truth or falsity of the church is irrelevant; it is an institution that must be preserved as the primary means of social control. Sounding like the inspiration for disgraced Chief Justice Roy Moore, Russell Kirk urges that, "state and church ought never to be separate entities, true religion is not merely an expression of national spirit; it rises far superior to earthly law, being, indeed, the source of all law". Kirk sees a difference between the faulty laws of man and the laws of God but never draws a distinction. I have to wonder if, like the modern Reconstructionist, Kirk wanted to see the laws of Leviticus imposed including executing homosexuals and blasphemers. He never explains how one might recognize a law of God besides using prejudice.

The third thread would be Kirk's anti-intellectual (or perhaps pro-stupid) stance. He refers to human reason as `puny' and `impotent' and claims that we find the mind of God in prejudice and tradition. `Prejudice', he writes, `is of ready application in the emergency; it previously engages the mind in a steady course of wisdom and virtue, and does not leave the man hesitating in the moment of decision, skeptical, puzzled, and unresolved'. Actually what he is advocating is for the general population to turn over rational thought to the church and those higher up the social chain. Citizens are encouraged to exhibit awe and veneration for God and those in higher stations and authority.

In order to grab the golden fleece of populism Conservatives have lately had to abandon overt stratification although veneration of wealth is certainly still evident. Like Calhoun the support for states rights remains a complete faade. I found Russell Kirk's salesmanship of Conservativism generally repellent but recommend the book because it remains a fairly enlightening view of an ideology that continues to thrive to this day.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0787978949:i_had_a_bad_feeling_about_this!__and_i_was_right!:z._fu
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
1974
</unique_id>
<asin>
0787978949
</asin>
<product_name>
Christian Wisdom of the Jedi Masters: Books: Dick Staub
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
I had a bad feeling about this!  And I was right!
</title>
<date>
December 4, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Z. Fu
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was intrigued by the title, which supposedly links Jedi wisdom to Christianity.  Well, after 60 pages or so, I have got the feeling that the Staub is trying to wrap Jedi in Christian cloth and failing at that. The author speaks of the difficulty in leading a Christian life.  But, I say that any religious life (be it Christian, Islam or otherwise) is hard because it turns the back on the norm or the conventional. 

I am convinced that Yoda is a Zen master; the Force is derived from Tao, not God as interpreted by the orthodox religion(I am purposefully leaving out Christian Mysticism, which is another beast altogether.). A better book on the subject of theology in Star wars is "The Dharma of Star Wars."
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
055380121X:lost_credability,_quickly!!:chalupa
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
4423
</unique_id>
<asin>
055380121X
</asin>
<product_name>
The Wisdom of Menopause: Creating Physical and Emotional Health and Healing During the Change: Books: Christiane Northrup
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Lost Credability, QUICKLY!!
</title>
<date>
July 10, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Chalupa
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Central California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I admit, I haven't finished this book.  A friend recommended it to me as I have been having problems with insomnia.  I was interested in reading a book about women's health issues and this one sounded intriguing UNTIL she started in with her tarot cards, interest in astrology and angels.  Granted, I am not a firm believer in just "the hard facts" but its really hard to believe anything this woman writes after it is clear that common sense isn't alternative enough for her!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0521662559:poorly_written:"dunner"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
5927
</unique_id>
<asin>
0521662559
</asin>
<product_name>
The Creation of America: Through Revolution to Empire: Books: Francis Jennings
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
6 of 22
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Poorly written
</title>
<date>
October 16, 2000
</date>
<reviewer>
"dunner"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Washington, DC USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I tried reading this book but found it so turgid and poorly written that I put it down in frustration.  It reads like a translation from another language by an academic bureacrat. The theme is interesting, the execution poor.  Cannot recommend
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0515136263:the_book_felt_more_like_the_author_was_forced_to_write_this_book:andromeda
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
6708
</unique_id>
<asin>
0515136263
</asin>
<product_name>
Chesapeake Blue: The Chesapeake Bay Saga #4: Books: Nora Roberts
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
The book felt more like the author was forced to write this book
</title>
<date>
December 31, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Andromeda
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Why is it ever time you want something bad enough it usually turns out bad? After the wonderful Quinn trilogy fans (including me) begged and begged for Nora Roberts to write Seth's story. After all we journeyed with Seth through we wanted to see him fall in love. Nora Roberts repeatedly said she would not write one. But us fans kept on begging for it and were excited when she finally gave in and wrote it. And we got Chesapeake Blue. Reading it you know you should be grateful because you wanted Seth's story but....this wasn't what I (and my fellow NR fans friends) wanted. First of all I wanted the heroine to be Aubrey. After their beautiful friendship in the Quinn trilogy I expected her to be Seth's love interest. But I tried to keep an open mind after all I loved Anna, Grace, and Sybill, but Dru Whitcomb Banks was a completely let down. All she did was whine and complain about her life which were minor compared to what Cam, Ethan, Philip, and Seth experienced as children. Seth becoming an artist was a surprise too I expected him to join the family business and design boats. The Gloria blackmailing him was a very thin and bad plotline. There's no reason Gloria would want to contact him considering all the warrents for her and that Seth wouldn't tell his family considering the Quinn Brothers (and wives)worked their so hard to keep him away from her. I closed this book vowing never to request, beg or petition an author to write a book when they say they don't want to. Because this is what you get
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
158322565X:the_islamo-fascists_murderers_thank_professor_chomsky!:raymond_p._keen
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
7182
</unique_id>
<asin>
158322565X
</asin>
<product_name>
11 de septiembre (9-11, Spanish-Language Edition): Books: Noam Chomsky
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
27 of 145
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
The Islamo-Fascists Murderers thank Professor Chomsky!
</title>
<date>
August 6, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Raymond P. Keen
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Noam Chomsky has thrived greatly in this great country of his, yours, and mine - the United States of America.  He has made millions of dollars teaching, lecturing, selling his books, and investing.  His world-wide fame in psycholinguistics is well-deserved.  His infamy is merited for his lack of loyalty to his own Jewish ethnicity and the U.S., in spite of the fruits he has received by being a citizen of the United States.  He has repaid this country in bile with his incredibly biased analysis of American foreign policy.  He goes way beyond a balanced multiculturism, when he always ranks the U.S. and Israel as foremost among the terrorist forces in the world now, and even in history.  His distrust of any authority, benign or otherwise, is reflected in his dogmatic and unexamined support of the "underdog," even if that underdog is a suicide bomber or a major terrorist organization such as Al Queda or Hezbollah.  

Yet since 1955, hypocrite Chomsky has worked for the "overdog" Massachusetts Institute of Technology, which has actively and enthusiastically participated in the development of weapons of War and mass destruction, and continues to this very day.

Chomsky trumps his own potential for gifted analytic objectivity with his simple hatred of the United States and the Jewish State.

If he were not so attached to the freedom of making money, earning the adulation of the American Left, and freedom to express himself, he might be able to give more direct and personal support for our enemies and his friends by taking up residence in North Korea, Iran, or Syria.  Let us hope he retires outside of our homeland that he hates so much, the United States of America.  

God Bless America, which will continue to give Chomsky the right to speak, teach, and make lots of money.

Raybo
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0451412095:stranded_on_an_island:k._m._halbig
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
7323
</unique_id>
<asin>
0451412095
</asin>
<product_name>
Murder at Five Finger Light: A Jessie Arnold Mystery: Books: Sue Henry
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Stranded on an Island
</title>
<date>
March 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
K. M. Halbig
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
California USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I have been a fan of Sue Henry since her first Jessie Arnold mystery.  I was looking forward to reading her lastest adventure, but was very disappointed in this outing.  The characters were one-dimensional.  After discovering who the "bad guys" were I needed to reread part of the book for clarification.  Sue Henry has a very annoying habit of foreshadowing at the end of many of her chapters.  "...they hadn't a notion just how decidedly things could - and would - change in the next few hours."  Even the relationship between Alex and Jessie seemed stilted.  I realize it is difficult to create plausible mysteries for a civilian like musher Jessie Arnold, but this book tried too hard and accomplished too little
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0441094996:another_self-indulgent_heinlein_novel:kenneth_p._albertson_"ken_a"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
8408
</unique_id>
<asin>
0441094996
</asin>
<product_name>
The Cat Who Walks Through Walls: Books: Robert A. Heinlein
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Another self-indulgent Heinlein novel
</title>
<date>
August 10, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Kenneth P. Albertson "Ken A"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Diego
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Heinlein loads this book up with hooks in the early pages to catch your attention.  Unfortunately, these hooks turn out to be superfluous and lead nowhere.  This shoddy technique is found in all four of Hienlein's final books.  We are also treated to some of Heinlein's stock characters, dirty old men, horny female computers, naked adolescent girls, and dominant beauties who would be right at home in leather and whips.  Without these archetype characters most Heinlein novels written after 1970 would have a sparse population indeed.  As if this isn't enough, Heinlein drags in his usual cast of characters from his other novels as he is so prone to doing.  In spite of all their cameo appearances, this group remains dull and one dimensional throughout.  Heinlein's earlier novels written prior to 1960 are still fine fare for young people, especially boys.  This novel, as well as most of Heinlein's later work will be enjoyed primarily by a group of die hard fans and is definitely not for general consumption
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0708919413:beautiful_beginning_/_painful_(illogical)_ending:ramu_nachiappan
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
8737
</unique_id>
<asin>
0708919413
</asin>
<product_name>
Sphere (Ulverscroft Large Print): Books: Michael Crichton
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Beautiful Beginning / Painful (illogical) Ending
</title>
<date>
July 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Ramu Nachiappan
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Ithaca, NY
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I hope the ending is illogical at least and is fiction. If thoughts are that powerful, they need to be resrained earlier. I don't know who survivied but he might feel very guilty about the others earlier and question if he had to survive. Logic can be quite painful when left alone, but sometimes it has to be
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0306813769:reading_shouldn't_have_to_be_a_chore:curtis_g
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
13989
</unique_id>
<asin>
0306813769
</asin>
<product_name>
Iron John: A Book About Men: Books: Robert Bly
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 19
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Reading shouldn't have to be a chore
</title>
<date>
May 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Curtis G
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
OC, CA, USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Once upon a time I was given a vanity-published book to review. It was an illogical mess, full of breathtaking non-sequiturs. While reading "Iron John," I couldn't help thinking of it. The vanity book, however, was at least entertaining.

John Eldredge refers to "Iron John" liberally in his book "Wild at Heart," and because I considered that a ringing endorsement, I purchased a copy. I can't tell you what a chore it has been to finally finish reading it. The hardest part was not flinging it away in disgust about 17 times.

It's one thing to write a rambling tome full of obscure references; it's another to publish it. That people can slog through it and call it "profound" and "important" is baffling; what's even more mind-boggling is that people claim that this book "spoke" to them. I think it's a case of "I'd better say I understand it, or people will think I'm not erudite." Well, let me be erudite about it: "Iron John" is a big, steaming pile of New Age crapola. Don't say I didn't warn you
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0060823879:dreadfully_boring:prairie_pal
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
14729
</unique_id>
<asin>
0060823879
</asin>
<product_name>
A Crack in the Edge of the World CD: America and the Great California Earthquake of 1906: Books: Simon Winchester,Winchester Simon
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
4 of 5
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Dreadfully Boring
</title>
<date>
April 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Prairie Pal
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Winnipeg, Canada
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
How can a best-selling author like Simon Winchester take an event as exciting as the San Francisco Earthquake of 1906 and turn it into a tedious snooze-fest? One answer: write as if you had just discovered an adjective mine and were free to throw in extra descripitive terms on every line until listeners scream for an end to florid phrases. Another: strive to break the record for most clich?s in a single paragraph. Finally: write about events in 1906 as if no one but Simon Winchester had ever before thought about their consequences -- thus, everything in this tedious narrative becomes about Simon. Simon and the raccoons; Simon on the failing American economy; Simon attempting to reproduce American accents. This is a CD set for avoiding
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1590072170:much_to_much_introspection:marvin_a._zimmer
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
19635
</unique_id>
<asin>
1590072170
</asin>
<product_name>
American Pastoral: Books: Philip Roth,Ron Silver
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
much to much introspection
</title>
<date>
August 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Marvin A. Zimmer
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
murray, ut United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I agree with the reviewer who said this work is boring. It seems Roth is trying to glorify Philip Roth and not the characters. He goes on and on describing the overwhelming feelings zuckermann has for "the swede", without letting us know who the Swede really is. Roth should let the characters tell the story or try to use less erudition in his narration.
It gets to the point where the reader loses interest in finishing the book. I loved the plot against american because it was more character based than philosophizing about about the historical context of the times
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1560257172:perhaps_the_worst_book_about_bono_or_u2_ever_written:aah412
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
19757
</unique_id>
<asin>
1560257172
</asin>
<product_name>
Bono: In the Name of Love: Books: Mick Wall
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
17 of 17
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Perhaps the worst book about Bono or U2 ever written
</title>
<date>
September 7, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
aah412
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oklahoma
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I echo the comments of the previous reviewers.  Don't waste your money.  Not only does this book present a tedious repetition of facts and stories already well known to even a casual U2 fan, it can't even get those facts right!  The book states that Bono's father dropped the family off at a Catholic Church before driving himself to another church.  This contradicts the correct statement on the preceding page that Bob Hewson was Catholic, while Bono, his mother and brother were Protestant.  In the same paragraph the Dublin neighborhood of "Glasnevin" is misspelled "Asnevin".  The hearing aid shop from which Bono took his name is misspelled, and perhaps most galling of all, the author can't even get the full name of Larry Mullen, Jr. right!  And this is just chapter one!  

I have to agree that this book was simply thrown together to make a quick buck and therefore not worth purchasing.  I would suggest skipping this one and purchasing Bono: In Conversation With Michka Assayas, which includes a pretty good account of Bono's life from the man himself. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1400054192:revenge!:mark_shook_"vmorrisey"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
19877
</unique_id>
<asin>
1400054192
</asin>
<product_name>
How to Talk to a Liberal (If You Must): The World According to Ann Coulter: Books: Ann Coulter
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 20
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Revenge!
</title>
<date>
September 6, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Mark Shook "vmorrisey"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Diego, CA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Let me see how many books can I write to preach to the choir about the same thing. She must of got dumped by a handful of Liberal boyfriends (what intellegent person would want her) and now she's trying to get back at 'em. Can't wait for the next "I hate liberals so much and here are my reasons why" book. She should join Fox she would fit right in
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1400054192:supports_the_partisan_divide_that_is_rotting_this_country_from_the_inside.:c._holcomb
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
19879
</unique_id>
<asin>
1400054192
</asin>
<product_name>
How to Talk to a Liberal (If You Must): The World According to Ann Coulter: Books: Ann Coulter
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 13
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Supports the partisan divide that is rotting this country from the inside.
</title>
<date>
August 28, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
C. Holcomb
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Raleigh, NC United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Anyone with intelligence can see that Ann Coulter is not attempting to make any meaningful or objective analysis of politics.  She is using inflammatory marketing to stir up the emotions of the most die-hard, flag-waving conservatives.  Until this attention-seeking labeling of other Americans as 'good' or 'bad' stops, there will never be true understanding of the complexties of American politics or foreign policy by the general public.  I don't agree with Bush's war and I didnt vote for him.  But he's not a 'bad person'; he did not invade Iraq because he is 'evil' or 'stupid'.  I can appreciate both sides of an argument; I can avoid generic categorizations.  I would never watch any news, liberal or conservative, that had a clear political bias.  Why can't Ann Coulter arrive at this same level of common sense?  Well, she wouldnt sell as many books; she wouldnt be on TV.  It has to be "Liberals Hate America" or "The Conservative Nazi Agenda".  We have the duty as thinking Americans, in the most advanced free country in the world, in these modern times of massive amounts of free information, to STOP PAYING ATTENTION TO THIS GARBAGE.  Get the facts and stop relying on a figurehead to spoon feed you your opinions
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0060735651:where_are_the_flags?_and_sound_effects?:jack,_but_my_students_call_me_emoth_(emo+goth=emoth)
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
20657
</unique_id>
<asin>
0060735651
</asin>
<product_name>
Let Freedom Ring: Winning the War of Liberty over Liberalism: Books: Sean Hannity
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
9 of 17
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Where are the flags? And sound effects?
</title>
<date>
July 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jack, but my students call me emoth (emo+goth=emoth)
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
emo+goth=emoth
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I remember hearing about this book by the great patriot Sean Hannity sometime in 2001, then it was a mere idea. From that time on, until August 20th 2002, I waited for what I thought would be the greatest book of all time. I remember seeing the cover art and hearing about the title: "Let Freedom Ring" with not just a picture of Sean Hannity on the cover, patriot that he is, but also a flag. I loved it, couldn't be more happy.

Well, the day of the book's release, I took a day off work (i've never missed a day of work before in my life), and rushed to get this book. It looked better than I ever imagined.

With the flag on the cover and the title of "Let Freedom Ring," I thought, finally, technology has caught up to our patriotism. I expected a book filled with flags, flags with sound effects. Maybe some firework sound effects. 

Boy was I wrong. I opened the book only to the colors black and white. No red. No blue. No stars and stripes. I quickly turned the pages, looking, searching for flags. I found none, no sound effects either, no fireworks. 

At that point, I went into a 4 year long depression. I nearly committed suicide at several points. It's only now that I can bring myself to review this man's book, patriot that he is. 

I say this so you know what you're getting yourself into. There are no flags, no stars and stripes, no fireworks, no sound effects. 

I have since recovered, but only because of old stars and stripes. I went back to teaching last year, not fully recovered, and my colleagues, knowing how much I love America and the STARS AND STRIPES, suggested I have my class do a research project: find the most patriotic book ever made. 

The methodoloy was simple: A book made out of flags with flag pictures would score high, a book that was not made out of a flag or flags and had no pictures of flags would score the lowest. 

We found some very good books and they did cheer me up. The one that was the most patriotic by far was a book called "President Jesus: How Jesus Wrote the Constitution, Freed the Slaves, and Won World War II." Its published by a small church in Texas. I was very proud of my students for finding it. It has brought countless joy to my life. Along with the book, made entirely out of a flag, with flag pictures, and written in blue and red ink, you get a giant flag. I'm not sure of the dimensions, but they had to haul it to my house in a moving truck. I've draped it over my house and it covers it completely. People even have to crawl under the flag to enter the house. 

Now I often go outside and just gaze at old stars and stripes for hours at a time, smiling.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0345467078:too_much_filler:bonner_'62
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
20951
</unique_id>
<asin>
0345467078
</asin>
<product_name>
Rage: An Alex Delaware Novel (Alex Delaware Novels (Paperback)): Books: Jonathan Kellerman
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Too Much Filler
</title>
<date>
April 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Bonner '62
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Virginia
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
All throughtout this book Alex Delaware and his police friend Milo never stop ruminating over every new fact they uncover.  They have endless discussions on how a new tidbit might fit into the overall picture.  The reader longs for the pair to actually do something.  In the end the author walks away without even tying up all the main strings.  That is really dirty pool after making the reader wade through all the yakking.  I read and enjoyed several of the early Alex Delaware books and then quit looking for new ones, now I know why
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0743555635:long_on_verbiage,_short_on_plot,_and_ultimately_pointless:d._r._jeanclerc_"reader,_listener_&_obsessive_observer"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
22660
</unique_id>
<asin>
0743555635
</asin>
<product_name>
The Ruins: Books: Scott Smith,Patrick Wilson
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Long on Verbiage, Short on Plot, and Ultimately Pointless
</title>
<date>
November 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
D. R. Jeanclerc "Reader, Listener & Obsessive Observer"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Brunswick, OH USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The book jacket for "The Ruins" offers a can't-miss premise:  a group of post-grad American tourists at play in Mexico jump at the chance for a little adventure among Mayan ruins but find but then find themselves in unimaginable danger.  It's the stuff of great Summer thrillers ready to be taken to the beach.  But 319 pages later, the reader is left to wonder whether or not the publisher put the wrong book in the jacket.  

Almost immediately, you'll notice that Smith's writing is as dense as the jungles that make the setting.  However, despite the endless stream of words, his descriptions are often threadbare.  Plus, there are no chapter breaks, which eventually pushes the pace until it feels like an assignment to continue.  

Next, the characters themselves begin to fall flat.  There are only really two couples to keep track of, and yet it's difficult for the first third of the book to distinguish them.  There is little to keep you interested in what they're doing or why they might be doing it.  Smith's attempts at developing these four as characters come in fits and spurts.  This seems obviously haphazard and hurried - the author is jamming in backstory whenever needed to explain characters' actions as if he were patching leaks in a dam.  By the end of the book, the foursome seems to be as disinterested in each other as the reader is in them.  

And for the readers who are hoping to discover something of interest in the setting such as Mayan mythology or archeological lore, forget it.  Aside from language barriers with the locals, there is no reason why this fantastical story couldn't have been set in the wilds of the Rocky Mountains, the Saharan desert, or anywhere else.  The danger posed has nothing to do with Mexico, archeology or mythology at all.  

Ah yes, the danger posed.  Well, I can't say much at all because anyone could give away the entire book with one line of explanation - that's how thin the plot is.  The numerous other reviews that fault this as a short story masquerading as a novel are exactly right.  Suffice it to say that when you do realize what the danger is (and you'll realize it well before any of the well-educated characters do), it's a real eye-roller, as if to say "I read this many pages for THIS?".

By the time the story concludes, it's more irritating than suspenseful.  The characters take so long to blithely undertake any course of action at all that you'll start rooting against them.  Eventually scenes of gore start piling up in an obvious and lazy attempt to interject some action, but even aside from being misdirected, it's too little too late.  

This book could have been an adventure, a supernatural thriller, a survival tale, or a horror screenplay.  It could have even taken the high road as an examination on people's reactions to situations of extreme stress:  some take the lead, even enjoying the challenge, while others whither into a shell of hopelessness.  But none of the possibilities ever come to fruition in this disappointing effort. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1596001836:too_graphic-too_long_to_get_somewhere:lizbeth
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
22784
</unique_id>
<asin>
1596001836
</asin>
<product_name>
Blue Smoke: Books: Nora Roberts,Joyce Bean
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Too Graphic-Too Long to get somewhere
</title>
<date>
August 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
LizBeth
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This book was so different from the usual NR story.  The burn scenes were too graphic and the rape scene was too graphic.  If you want romance, skip this.  It also seemed to take forever to get the book set up
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0839824491:great_premise,_terrible_execution:matthew_w._grieco
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
23091
</unique_id>
<asin>
0839824491
</asin>
<product_name>
I Will Fear No Evil (Gregg Press Science Fiction Series): Books: Robert A. Heinlein
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Great premise, terrible execution
</title>
<date>
July 29, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Matthew W. Grieco
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York City
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This book is offensive to at least one of the two genders, though it's hard to say which. It suggests that a man whose brain was transplanted into that of a sensual woman would become a wanton harlot, more or less. Whether that's more insulting to the male brain or the female body, I'm not sure, but the book portrays neither gender realistically.

I like Heinlein, and the first 100 or so pages of this book show a lot of potential, but after that the book descends into vapid sexual morass, and it's not even particularly good at being that.

The gender-swapping theme has been a common one in fiction and film in the last 30 years or so, but Heinlein joined the ranks of the many authors and directors who treated it as a chance to write pseudo-enlightened erotica instead of literature. More's the pity
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0345362462:for_fanatics_only:the_sanity_inspector_"the_sanity_inspector"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
23126
</unique_id>
<asin>
0345362462
</asin>
<product_name>
Grumbles from the Grave: Books: Robert A. Heinlein
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
For fanatics only
</title>
<date>
May 20, 2001
</date>
<reviewer>
The Sanity Inspector "the_sanity_inspector"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Why in the world would anyone publish a writer's bread and butter notes to his agent?  Besides the money, I mean.  There are a couple or three interesting fulminations against this publisher or that editor, whom Heinlein feels did him dirty.  But in the main this body of correspondence is of zero interest to any but the most complete worshipers of the sf master.  Just enjoy the stories, and nevermind the workaday business of how they got published
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0399152830:two_thumbs_down:kathie
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
23703
</unique_id>
<asin>
0399152830
</asin>
<product_name>
Predator (Kay Scarpetta Mysteries): Books: Patricia Cornwell
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Two Thumbs Down
</title>
<date>
November 20, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Kathie
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I thought it was me until I read several other reviews of Predator.  Ms. Cornwell can do so much better than this disjointed mess.  If she's going to continue the Scarpetta series, she needs to get back on track, creating characters that we care about.  I finished this book as quickly as possible just to get it behind me.  What a disappointment
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0399152830:please_do_not_read:joseph_r._swift
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
23712
</unique_id>
<asin>
0399152830
</asin>
<product_name>
Predator (Kay Scarpetta Mysteries): Books: Patricia Cornwell
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Please do NOT read
</title>
<date>
October 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Joseph R. Swift
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I did not finish the book (I got about 70% of the way through before I realized I could not bear to read one more page).  Maybe the remaining part of the book would have been better, but I doubt it.  This is the first time I can ever remember not even having even the slightest interesting in finishing a book.  The characters were flat and plot went nowhere.  Please - there are million of books out there.  Spare yourself, and find something else to read. Anything.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
030726419X:avidreader:a.g.g._"avidreader"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
24124
</unique_id>
<asin>
030726419X
</asin>
<product_name>
The Emperor's Children: Books: Claire Messud
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
avidreader
</title>
<date>
November 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A.G.G. "avidreader"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
canada
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This is an overwritten and overhyped piece of fiction that will never pass for great literature. It is timely but it is not timeless.  

Not one character comes alive even though they all talk endlessly. Not one scene is memorable. The true nature of the book -- soap opera-- is cloaked under its many pages.   Messud is a good writer who in this instance could not tell a good story, and she seems to have believed her publicity machine.  I can't believe that her husband, who a great literary critic, would not talk her out of publishing this.  Oh.  I forgot.  Money and fame trumps quality every time.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000G5SBFU:not_good:barb
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
25963
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000G5SBFU
</asin>
<product_name>
The Five People You Meet in Heaven: Books: Mitch Albom
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Not good
</title>
<date>
November 12, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Barb
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Michigan
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I thought the title was interesting so I bought this book.  Wow, what a disappointment.  This is sappy and poorly written.  How does Mitch Albom keep  getting on the best sellers list
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
055338080X:lost_credability,_quickly!!:chalupa
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
26778
</unique_id>
<asin>
055338080X
</asin>
<product_name>
The Wisdom of Menopause: Books: Christiane Northrup
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
12 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Lost Credability, QUICKLY!!
</title>
<date>
July 10, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Chalupa
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Central California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I admit, I haven't finished this book.  A friend recommended it to me as I have been having problems with insomnia.  I was interested in reading a book about women's health issues and this one sounded intriguing UNTIL she started in with her tarot cards, interest in astrology and angels.  Granted, I am not a firm believer in just "the hard facts" but its really hard to believe anything this woman writes after it is clear that common sense isn't alternative enough for her!
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1401202012:battle_of_the_sexes-how_the_world_falls_apart_once_it's_entrusted_to_women:govagabndgrl_"dodovagabndr"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
27236
</unique_id>
<asin>
1401202012
</asin>
<product_name>
Y: The Last Man Vol. 3: One Small Step: Books: Brian K. Vaughan,Pia Guerra,Jose Marzan,Brian V. Vaughan,Pia Guerra,Jose Marzan
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
0 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
BATTLE OF THE SEXES-how the world falls apart once it's entrusted to women
</title>
<date>
September 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
govagabndgrl "dodovagabndr"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
pueblo, CO U.S.A.
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
You all like misogynist comics
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1400030277:bitter_discontinuities:supertango
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
28377
</unique_id>
<asin>
1400030277
</asin>
<product_name>
A Continent for the Taking: The Tragedy and Hope of Africa: Books: Howard W. French
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 8
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
bitter discontinuities
</title>
<date>
March 5, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
supertango
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
paris
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
despite early promise, marked by intriguing personal observations and evident self-reflection, this effort fails to deliver on the author's experience and acumen.  the book is a disparate set of chapters and lacks a unitary thread, apart from a bitter leavening of asides on the shortcomings of United States rhetoric and policies on Africa.  i had hoped for more, given the fine record in newsprint of this well-traveled journalist.

</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0771577206:not_impressed_with_this_one!:tara
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
30537
</unique_id>
<asin>
0771577206
</asin>
<product_name>
The Mother of All Pregnancy Books: An All-Canadian Guide to Conception, Birth and Everything in Between: Books: Ann Douglas
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 6
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not Impressed with this one!
</title>
<date>
June 4, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Tara
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Canada
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I read some raving reviews about this book, but I admit, I was quite disappointed.  Factual, I'm sure, but it lacks details and tries to touch on too much without going into any depth.  Many other pregnancy books go into further detail
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
B000F5ZH3A:left_me_wanting_more...:heidi_"tomb_lily"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
31695
</unique_id>
<asin>
B000F5ZH3A
</asin>
<product_name>
Chill Factor : A Novel: Books: Sandra Brown
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Left me wanting more...
</title>
<date>
September 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Heidi "Tomb Lily"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Oshkosh, WI
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The characters are uninteresting and 2-dimensional, the dialog hackneyed. I have no idea why it's on the New York Times Bestseller list. It was more of an obligation for me to finish this book than anything else. Don't waste your money
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0446606189:mailing_it_in:ryan_mcgovern
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
32464
</unique_id>
<asin>
0446606189
</asin>
<product_name>
Cat & Mouse (Alex Cross Novels): Books: James Patterson
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
7 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Mailing it in
</title>
<date>
October 25, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
RYAN MCGOVERN
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Boston, MA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I've been following the Alex Cross series from its beginning, and after reading Cat & Mouse, I'm wondering if Patterson has taken these characters as far as they can go... Given the fact that there are 7 or 8 more Cross books written subsequently to this one, I can only hope that the series gets better.

My complains are similar to those of other reviewers:

1. I'm getting sick of the perfection of Alex Cross.  The man's a saintly father, saintly grandson, saintly lover, saintly charity worker, and saintly detective.  These traits hooked the reader and made Cross an intriguing character, but he's fast becoming too one-dimensional.

2. The Cross/Sampson relationship.  As if we weren't sick enough of this already.  Every few chapters, we're reminded of the man-crush Cross and Sampson have on each other.  Sampson is so perfect in Cross's eyes that it becomes tiresome to hear about it every time Sampson enters a scene.

3. The Cross/Christine Johnson relationship moves WAY too fast.  One moment Christine is still mourning the loss of her husband (who was viciously murdered 6 months prior in Jack & Jill) and freaks out over an innocent dinner date, and the next she and Cross are madly in love.  No development whatsoever, no line from Point A to Point B.

4. I'm not sure Patterson could have written the dialogue between Cross and his children any more unrealistically.  Aren't these 7- and 9-year-old children?  He has more intelligent conversations with his kids than he does with Sampson or Kyle Craig.

5. The entire novel is a series of pseudo-climaxes which are ultimately resolved by plot twists that seemingly arrive from left field.  The Soneji resolution was anti-climactic at best, and the Mr. Smith conclusion was unfulfilling
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0380719088:_sniveling_condescending_left_wing_diatribe:bruce_kirkpatrick_"bk_mcstuff"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
34176
</unique_id>
<asin>
0380719088
</asin>
<product_name>
Don't Know Much About the Civil War: Everything You Need to Know About America's Greatest Conflict but Never Learned (Don't Know Much About...(Paperback)): Books: Kenneth C. Davis
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 25
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
 Sniveling condescending Left wing diatribe
</title>
<date>
August 30, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Bruce Kirkpatrick "bk_mcstuff"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
the worktable on my boat
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If you are looking for a book that does a cover to cover job of bashing western civilization with complete and obvious bias, this is it.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0375416269:definitely_not_up_there_with_krakauer!:lisa_bahrami
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
34393
</unique_id>
<asin>
0375416269
</asin>
<product_name>
The Last River: Books: Todd Balf,Dennis Boutsikaris
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Definitely not up there with Krakauer!
</title>
<date>
June 6, 2003
</date>
<reviewer>
Lisa Bahrami
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
orlando, fl USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
One of the blurbs I read on the book jacket compared this book to Into Thin Air and The Perfect Storm. No way!. Those two books were edge-of-your-seat reading experiences. This account of a kayaking expedition is just plain boring. The action doesn't start until about halfway or more into the book and even then, the cliched writing and deification of Balf's subjects make this book very hard to get through. Unless you are a serious kayaking fan, I would not recommend this book
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0446601888:editorial_standards_are_certainly_lacking:paul_denize
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
36025
</unique_id>
<asin>
0446601888
</asin>
<product_name>
Eternity: Books: Greg Bear
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
5 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Editorial standards are certainly lacking
</title>
<date>
August 10, 2000
</date>
<reviewer>
Paul Denize
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Zealand
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I had somewhat forgotten how Greg Bear wrote.  His descriptions of the  Jart are so obscure and long-winded, the reader may as well just turn the  page.  I found it annoying that Greg Bear attempted to invent even more  words in this book than Eon.  My largest complaint however resided in the  high number of typos, duplicated words, letters dropped etc that made the  reading even more disruptive.  It really looked like there had been global  replacements as the same errors were repeated.  While I'd admit that an  author is more concerned with flow, plot, and technical accuracy - the  editor should review with a little more care to the fundamentals
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0312239572:big_disapointment:marsha__haas
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
37441
</unique_id>
<asin>
0312239572
</asin>
<product_name>
The Martyrs of Columbine: Faith and the Politics of Tragedy: Books: Justin Watson
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
8 of 12
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Big disapointment
</title>
<date>
July 3, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Marsha  Haas
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Michigan,USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was very disapointed in the book.Basicly the writer took bits and pieces from books written by others,twisted their words and put his own spin on it.It repeats itself over and over being so repetative I had to put it down.There are good books out there written by people who were there.I suggest you take a look at those.I read many good one's but this book wasnt in that catagory
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0743564537:not_great_at_all.:jb_"jb"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
39440
</unique_id>
<asin>
0743564537
</asin>
<product_name>
Peter Pan in Scarlet: Books: Geraldine McCaughrean,Tim Curry
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not great at all.
</title>
<date>
October 22, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
JB "JB"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
LA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This story is very dark, full of menace and dark thoughts. Not great for kids. OK for adults if that's what you like. A hard story, not much gentleness in it except for a couple of moments
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0765349655:better_than_crichton???:jayson_d._white_"reader"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
41530
</unique_id>
<asin>
0765349655
</asin>
<product_name>
Tyrannosaur Canyon: Books: Douglas Preston
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Better than Crichton???
</title>
<date>
October 16, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Jayson D. White "Reader"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Albuquerque, NM
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Many reviewers compared this novel to Jurassic Park, saying it was a better book than Crichton's. What absurdity. I am not saying that JP is an awesome book, but it was far better than Tyrannosaur Canyon.

Tyrannosaur Canyon is a fairly intriguing story, but poorly executed and VERY poorly ended. It's as though Preston suddenly realized that he was going to have to get his characters out of the predicament he had put them in, and didn't know how to do it. The ending is too fast, too unlikely and too unrealistic.

The book closes with a theistic comment by one of the characters, which I believe is Preston's way of attempting to belong to both camps, having his science AND being religious.

Overall, I had high hopes for this book and I am sorry to say that in the last 100 pages, I was greatly let down

</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0743504739:more_quotes_and_facts,_less_opinions_and_emotions.:l._mihalkovic
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
44389
</unique_id>
<asin>
0743504739
</asin>
<product_name>
John Adams: Books: David McCullough,Edward Herrmann
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
More quotes and facts, less opinions and emotions.
</title>
<date>
September 5, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
L. Mihalkovic
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Vancouver/Toronto - CA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
First of all, I did not exactly 'read' this biography. Instead I purchased the CD version which I distilled via my car sound system every morning on my way to work (I have enjoyed countless biographies of great american figures this way, and still been able to read many more technology related books).

I had great expectations from this book, having recently enjoyed three biographies of Lincoln. I have to confess that I was sorely disapointed. I found the research of Mr McCullough to lack the kind of details that I have enjoyed in biographies from Walter Isaacson, Richard Carwardine, or Doris Goodwin. I do not seek a beautiful story in a biography, but rather a reliable source of facts that I can use to form my own opinion of a character. In this context, I find Mr McCullough's use of superlatives or long emotionally charged sentences to be a distraction from the subject matter of John Adams and his contribution to America. I also enjoy direct quotes from letters, speaches, autobiographies, as they help me refine my impressions of the context (the period, the relationships to contemporary characters, ...) surounding a promonent figure. Usage of the English language in politics has dramatically evolved since Mr Adams' time, and I missed 'hearing' the voice of John Adams. Instead, this biography felt like reading a translation where the personality of the translator overshadows the personality of the original author. Finally, having read other biographies of the founding fathers, I was disapointed to find so little about the complex relationship between Adams and Franklin.

All in all, my lasting impression is that Mr McCullough did a great job at bringing John Adams and the early American Revolution to the masses through a very appealling product that may however leave readers asking for more historical details and less emotional opinions. Had I known that, I might have passed on this biography and instead explore Mr McCullough's fictional work
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0521556325:historical_fiction:jill_malter
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
47580
</unique_id>
<asin>
0521556325
</asin>
<product_name>
A History of Modern Palestine: One Land, Two Peoples: Books: Ilan Pappe
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 94
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Historical fiction
</title>
<date>
August 22, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Jill Malter
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
jillmalter@aol.com
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
This simply isn't history.  In real life, people do things for reasons.  Historians explain what happened and (to some extent) why.  That is how they are able to infer as yet unknown details and even predict future attitudes and acts.  Pappe gets plenty of facts wrong, but his biggest failing is to ascribe incorrect or even impossible motives to many of the people of the region.

This book is propaganda masquerading as history. 
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0060957239:i_had_to_stop_reading_this_book_it_upset_me_so_much:monika_"monikaorinda"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
47859
</unique_id>
<asin>
0060957239
</asin>
<product_name>
When You're Expecting Twins, Triplets, or Quads: A Complete Resource (Harperresource Books): Books: Barbara Luke,Tamara Eberlein
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
I had to stop reading this book it upset me so much
</title>
<date>
August 2, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Monika "monikaorinda"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
SF Bay Area
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I know a lot of people liked this book, but I felt like it put too much pressure on me to pack on the pounds.  I didn't realise so much of the book was focused on diet.  It says you should plan on gaining a pound a week, and the more you gain the healthier your babies will be.  Well the first 13 weeks I managed to gain NOTHING, and I felt horrible about it, but food made me so sick the last thing I could do was eat MORE food to try to gain weight.  The book said that according to my starting weight I should try to gain 50 - 60 pounds during my pregnancy!  I decided to stop reading the book, and so far, just going by what my gut says about what to eat and when, I've managed to put on 20 pounds.  My twins are measuring perfectly and are very healthy.

This book isn't horrible, but I would check it out of a library or borrow it or buy it used, don't spend the $ on a new one... and be prepared to put it down if it doesn't sound right to you
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0205325238:terrible_for_independent_study:j._chen
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
48548
</unique_id>
<asin>
0205325238
</asin>
<product_name>
Abnormal Psychology and Modern Life: Books: Robert C. Carson
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>

</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
terrible for independent study
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
J. Chen
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Though this book does present all the necessary information for learning about abnormal psychology, it's the dryest, most aesthetically difficult to read textbook... especially if you happen to be studying the material online/through independent study.  The publisher needs to redesign the book and/or you need to have a better online course professor. It feels nearly impossible to be interested in this material (which is interesting in itself) if you have to read the textbook front to back on your own without any instruction.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0143034332:dry_as_the_arabian_desert:rajiv_k._agrawala
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
49546
</unique_id>
<asin>
0143034332
</asin>
<product_name>
A History of the Middle East: Second Edition: Books: Peter Mansfield,Nicolas Pelham
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 11
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Dry as the Arabian desert
</title>
<date>
April 21, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Rajiv K. Agrawala
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Warren, MI USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I bought this audio CD set at the Borders store, without the opportunity to preview the narration. Had I been able to do so, I probably never would have purchased it, let alone paid full bookstore price for it. But I needed an audiobook for my long drive the next day, so I relented. 

Lesson learned.

The audio quality is very insonsistent, at at times very poor, having been transcribed from the original audiotape recording. 

While the author is obviously greatly informed on the historical and geopolitical details of the Middle East, it does read very much like a history text. With the amount of detail presented, and the wide scope of coverage from one end of Europe reaching into the former Soviet states and beyond, one immediately feels the need for visual aids (maps, timelines, etc.) as guidance. 

The reader's narration is monotononous, with a very constant cadence which dulls the senses. Each sentence sounds the same as the last. This has the unfortunate effect of rendering each piece of information presented as no more significant than any other, and so all of the events seem to be lost to obscurity. After a while, the narration becomes little more than background noise. No information is retained by the listener
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0898799082:fluffy_and_elevated_-_not_for_writers_with_a_story_to_tell:scott_w._baker_"oso_muerte"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
50573
</unique_id>
<asin>
0898799082
</asin>
<product_name>
Description (Elements of Fiction Writing): Books: Monica Wood
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
10 of 15
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Fluffy and elevated - not for writers with a story to tell
</title>
<date>
September 5, 2005
</date>
<reviewer>
Scott W. Baker "Oso Muerte"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Monterey, TN United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Nothing in this book was usable for me.  Okay, very little.  If I was trying to write the next _Ethan Frome_, then this book would be perfect.  Instead I write sci-fi and fantasy.  I was looking for tips to improve my description of things; this book recommends describing different things.  Too much emphasis on metaphor (which is a wonderful tool but a tad obvious).  If you want to write in a way people might actually communicate, this book might be a waste of your time.  HOWEVER, poets and pure-literary writers might find it more useful than I did
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1586217070:not_worth_the_25-cent_cost:loves_a_good_thriller_"gina"
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
51776
</unique_id>
<asin>
1586217070
</asin>
<product_name>
Hour Game: Books: David Baldacci,Scott Brick
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 2
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not Worth the 25-Cent Cost
</title>
<date>
October 13, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Loves a Good Thriller "Gina"
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
San Pedro, California
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
When I found "Hour Game" in paperback at our local library's monthly book sale, I thought I had hit pay dirt.  But I cannot believe that this author who wrote such gripping gems such as "The Winner" and "Absolute Power" could turn out such a dog.  Long, boring, and confusing.  I fear that Mr. Baldacci hired an "aspiring young writer" to "help" him crank out a quick book. I cannot pass this book along to my friends -- I couldn't do that to them.  It will be tossed into our blue recycle bin.  What a waste.  What a shame.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
047142997X:just_a_disorganized,_lifeless,_inspid_mass_of_business_memo._:sei_kameoka
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
52702
</unique_id>
<asin>
047142997X
</asin>
<product_name>
Disconnected: Deceit and Betrayal at WorldCom: Books: Lynne W. Jeter
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
3 of 3
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Just a disorganized, lifeless, inspid mass of business memo. 
</title>
<date>
February 4, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Sei Kameoka
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New Hampshire
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
I was expecting this book to be a great story, but very disappointed. I cannot believe the publisher allowed the author to publish this book as it is. The book is insipid and dull,  has no flow, no story, or no plot. Let me present an example. I have read many insightful Newsweek articles by a writer Allan Sloan. For example, Sloan describes a Sprint merger event in this way, "If talk is getting cheaper, why did MCI WorldCom pay $115 billion to buy Sprint? The once staid phone companies have launched a merger blitzkrieg in an effort to emerge at the center of the wired world. Can regulators handle the complex new order....."  It has a clear logical axis, and has a force to attract readers into it. 

But Jeter describes it like this,  "The merger announcement of WorldCom and Sprint spurred building activity around Worldcom headquarters as real estate developers readied for economic prosperity. The real estate inventory swelled with new planned unit....." It always presents off-center, trivial detail which makes a reader bored. 70% of books are consumed to described a dry and dull fact, like "the merger of company A & B raised the stock to $X" etc. There is no insight here. 

But unfortunately, unlike Enron scandal, there is no other book that centered on the Worldcom scandal. You would get much better comprehension by collecting articles in Newsweek or Business Week, if you have LexisNexis or EBISCOhost.
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
158115321X:not-so-creative_canine_photography:a._c._hardester
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
53422
</unique_id>
<asin>
158115321X
</asin>
<product_name>
Creative Canine Photography: Books: Larry Allan
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
2 of 7
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Not-So-Creative Canine Photography
</title>
<date>
April 8, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
A. C. Hardester
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Philadelphia, PA United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
If you are interested in a very traditional approach from a professional photographer, this book will provide lots of information.  It also provides valuable tips about controlling the dog.  But  for my taste, I found the photographic results to be uninspiring - too much posing, too much portraiture lighting, not enough of just plain capturing that  wonderful dog as it is
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0385338260:too_bad_to_finish:happy_reader
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
53431
</unique_id>
<asin>
0385338260
</asin>
<product_name>
Impossible: Books: Danielle Steel
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 1
</helpful>
<rating>
1.0
</rating>
<title>
Too Bad to Finish
</title>
<date>
October 27, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Happy Reader
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
Northridge, CA USA
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
The worst book I've read (actually, I was listening to the audiobook).  The characters are completely unbelievable and the book is so repetetive that I found myself YELLING at the tape player, "I KNOW, I KNOW ALREADY".  I couldn't stand the torture anymore, I didn't even finish it.  I have enjoyed some of DS's earlier work, but will not buy another
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
1589268555:sel:sarah_e._lewis
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
55700
</unique_id>
<asin>
1589268555
</asin>
<product_name>
Captivating: Unveiling The Mystery Of A Woman's Soul: Books: John Eldredge,Stasi Eldredge
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
1 of 4
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
sel
</title>
<date>
November 9, 2006
</date>
<reviewer>
Sarah E. Lewis
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>

</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Was not impressed.  Narrow scoped, personal reflections, applications limited.  I also read the male companion book Wild at heart and was also not impressed
</review_text>
</review>
<review>
<unique_id>
0312239548:poorly_edited_and_often_non-sensical:ricky_hunter
</unique_id>
<unique_id>
56790
</unique_id>
<asin>
0312239548
</asin>
<product_name>
The Happiest Corpse I've Ever Seen: The Last Twenty-Five Years of the Broadway Musical: Books: Ethan Mordden
</product_name>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<product_type>
books
</product_type>
<helpful>
16 of 19
</helpful>
<rating>
2.0
</rating>
<title>
Poorly Edited and Often Non-sensical
</title>
<date>
November 2, 2004
</date>
<reviewer>
Ricky Hunter
</reviewer>
<reviewer_location>
New York City, NY United States
</reviewer_location>
<review_text>
Ethan Mordden's editors have allowed him to ruin what could possibly have been a good book.  This is the worst of his books on the various decades of the Broadway musical as the faults of the seventies book have widened into gulfs.  His political ramblings (often just slightly right of Ann Coulter and making as much sense) seep through the book, dragging it down.  The French people are slammed a number of times, along with the ACLU, Burt Lancaster (apparently, according to Ethan a good friend of Stalin) and the left in general, while the author defends Bush (and it does take some looking back over the page to figure out how he fits all this into a book on musical theatre).  The author's train of thought wanders like a bitter old man  all over the page in search of a target, any target.  It is often hard to stomach.  The truly sad fact about this is that the author often has quite cogent things to say about a particular musical and when he does stick to that, it can actually make one want to look at the work again.  An editor should have cleaned the work up before before allowing it on stage to greet its public.  The author is capable of better work
</review_text>
</review>